GORAN RADMANOVIC

Senior Front End Developer

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm a web developer, who likes new technologies, challenges and new experience and I'm a guick learner. You can easily find me and contact me through social accounts or on email address. It would be a great honor to work with you.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER, THE SITE DOCTOR - TSD MAY 2023 - SEP 2024

LEAD FRONT END DEVELOPER, TRIVIAL APR 2024 - PRESENT

FRONT END DEVELOPER. THE SITE DOCTOR - TSD DEC 2023 - FEB 2024

FRONT END DEVELOPER, FREELANCE MAY 2023 - DEC 2023

FRONT END DEVELOPER, DIGIMONDO MAY 2021 - MAY 2023

FRONT END DEVELOPER, EXAMIZ DEC 2020 - AVG 2021

WEB DEVELOPER, WEBIMPACTO JUN 2020 - JUN 2021

WEB DEVELOPER, OOMOVERS JUL 2019 - JUL 2021

OTHER EXPERIENCE

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/#experience

PROJECTS

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/#projects

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- VueJS
- NuxtJS
- PHP & MySQL
- HTML & CSS
- SASS
- **GIT**
- **PWA**
- SPA
- Laravel
- Veutify
- **Bootstrap**
- **TailwindCSS**
- NodeJS
- **Firebase**



CONTACT

goranradmanovic@gmail.com

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/goranradmanovic-70814a9b/

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Faculty of Sciences, BSc University in Banja Luka

COURSES

- Basic Course Of Javascript, ICBL
- Basic Course Of PHP & MySQL, ICBL
- Basic Course Of Java, ICBL
- OOP Course In PHP, INFOARS
- Advanced Course In PHP, INFOARS
- Beginning Course In PHP, INFOARS
- WordPress Course, ICBL
- Team Work Course, ICBL

LANGUAGES

- Serbian / Bosnian / Croatian
- English (C2)

HOBBIES

- Running
- Cycling
- **Blood donor**